<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speakers on Joy of Coding</title>
    <link>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speakers on Joy of Coding</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Joy of Coding 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 20:01:07 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AIsland</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/a-i-sland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 20:01:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/a-i-sland/</guid>
      <description>By Dion van Dam
During the conference, the huge video wall will be running an AI programming challenge. Code your own bot on your laptop and watch it compete with other people’s bots on the big screen.
AIsland is a turn-based strategy game for 2-8 bot players, entered for each round by their humans. The winner of each round is the bot that successfully takes over the generated island landscape by removing the other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carin Meier</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/carin-meier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 20:01:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/carin-meier/</guid>
      <description>The Joy of Stochastic Gradient Descent We’ll take a look at the joys of Deep Learning from its simple, elegant fundamentals to its feats of impressive power. Along the way, we’ll discuss how Deep Learning is changing how we approach programming, communicate with each other, and even what it means to be human.
On Twitter she is known as @gigasquid</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessica Kerr</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/jessica-kerr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 20:01:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/jessica-kerr/</guid>
      <description>Shaving the Golden Yak Programming is a series of frustrations. Everything we do, we could do better or faster if we only had our tools set up just so. If our error messages were a little better, our code a little cleaner, our tests a lot wider. How do you balance the work you’re supposed to be doing with the work that makes your work, work? Dive into the yak stack with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Koshin Mariano</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/koshin-mariano/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 20:01:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/koshin-mariano/</guid>
      <description>Talk title to be announced On Twitter he is known as @Koshin_M</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Llewellyn Falco</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/llewellyn-falco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 20:01:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/llewellyn-falco/</guid>
      <description>Mob Programming If you think pair programming (2 people on 1 computer) is crazy, hold onto your hats; it’s time for Mob Programming.
Mob Programming: All the brilliant people working on the same thing, at the same time, in the same place, and on the same computer.
We are going to take a look at a new way of working, what it looks like, and why it can work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neal Ford</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/neal-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 20:01:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/neal-ford/</guid>
      <description>Stories Every Developer Should Know  &amp;ldquo;Those who cannot remember the past are condemned to repeat it.&amp;rdquo; – George Santayana 
 &amp;ldquo;The past is never dead. It’s not even past.&amp;rdquo; – William Faulkner 
Most architects and developers pursue the Latest and Greatest with great fervor, yet the history of engineering, including software projects, contains rich lessons that we risk repeating ad nauseam. This keynote recounts a variety of stories of projects that failed architecturally…and why.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed Meeting</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/speed-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 20:01:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/speed-meeting/</guid>
      <description>By Linda van der Pal
Whether you’ve never attended a developer conference before, or if you’ve been around the circuit for years, occasionally they can be a lonely experience.
Joy of Coding tries to remove that feeling with a session of Speed Meeting. In this session you will introduce yourself to several other conference attendees in short introductions of a few minutes each. In this introduction you are invited to talk with one other participant about who you both are, and why you are here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Neward</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/ted-neward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 20:01:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/speaker/ted-neward/</guid>
      <description>Talk title to be announced On Twitter he is @tedneward</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>