<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Joy of Coding</title>
    <link>http://joyofcoding.org/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Joy of Coding</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Joy of Coding 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 12:38:11 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://joyofcoding.org/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 12:38:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/about/</guid>
      <description>We are organising for fun, not for profit. The people behind Joy of Coding are an informal group, backed by a legal entity (the Devnology Foundation). We are organising this for fun, not for profit.
   Felienne
Hermans I am assistant professor and speaker. I strive to make programming better and easier for non-programmers. I love functional programming and board games.
 @felienne  Arne
Timmerman Software engineer and community facilitator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 12:38:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating the art, craft, science and joy of software development ―&amp;nbsp; Code of Conduct
    All attendees, speakers, hosts, sponsors and volunteers (all these further referred to as participants) at our events are subject to the following code of conduct. We will enforce this code throughout all our events and are expecting cooperation from all participants to help ensuring a safe environment for everybody.  No harrassment We are dedicated to providing harassment-free events for everyone, regardless of gender, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, or religion (or lack thereof).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joining instructions</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/instructions-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 12:38:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/instructions-speakers/</guid>
      <description>Speaker instructions Practical information for Joy of Coding 2017 speakers.
   Please see the attendee joining instructions for more information.
 Arrival in Rotterdam The six main conference speakers are staying five minutes’ walk from the venue.
Hotel address: Rotterdam Marriott Hotel, Weena 686, 3012CN Rotterdam
Speakers’ dinner The six main conference speakers can meet each other and the organisers before the pre-party for dinner at a Thai restaurant, 17:30-19:00.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joining instructions</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/instructions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 12:38:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/instructions/</guid>
      <description>Joining instructions Practical information for all conference attendees and speakers.
   Before the conference Follow the speakers on Twitter, via our Joy of Coding 2017 list.
Sign-up for the pre-party, on Thursday evening in Rotterdam.
Read the conference Code of Conduct.
 What to take Take a laptop for the AIsland coding challenge.
Getting there Address: Rotterdamse Schouwburg, Schouwburgplein 25, 3012 CL Rotterdam
By plane/train: get the train to Rotterdam Central Station and walk 8 minutes to the venue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule 2017</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 12:38:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/schedule/</guid>
      <description>  Hi there, have a look at our 2017 schedule! Have a look at al the inspiring speakers that will come to Rotterdam on 30 June. Most slots are links to more detailed information.
  08:30 - 09:20  08:30 - 09:20  Walk in @ Main hall   08:30 - 09:20  Registration @ Foyer      09:20 - 09:30  09:20 - 09:30  Opening and introduction to the AIsland Game Contest @ Main hall       09:30 - 10:10  Keynote09:30 - 10:10  Living the good life Ted Neward@ Main hall        10:10 - 10:50   10:10 - 10:50  Break @ Foyer   Game10:10 - 10:50  AIsland Game Contest @ Foyer      10:50 - 11:30  Talk10:50 - 11:30  Shaving the golden yak Jessica Kerr@ Main hall     Game10:50 - 11:30  AIsland Game Contest @ Foyer      11:30 - 12:10  Community11:30 - 12:10  Lightning talks @ Main hall    Networking11:30 - 12:10  Speed meeting @ Foyer       12:10 - 13:10   12:10 - 13:10  Lunch @ Foyer   Game12:10 - 13:10  AIsland Game Contest @ Foyer      13:10 - 13:50  Keynote13:10 - 13:50  Stories every developer should know Neal Ford@ Main hall        13:50 - 14:30  Talk13:50 - 14:30  Mob programming Llewellyn Falco@ Main hall     Game13:50 - 14:30  AIsland Game Contest @ Foyer      14:30 - 15:10   14:30 - 15:10  Break @ Foyer   Game14:30 - 15:10  AIsland Game Contest @ Foyer      15:10 - 15:50  Talk15:10 - 15:50  How to hire and work with people who aren’t like you Koshin Mariano@ Main hall     Game15:10 - 15:50  AIsland Game Contest @ Foyer      15:50 - 16:30  Keynote15:50 - 16:30  The joy of stochastic gradient descent Carin Meier@ Main hall        16:30 - 16:50  16:30 - 16:50  RoboCup Junior demo @ Main hall        16:50 - 20:00   16:50 - 20:00  Drinks/dinner @ Foyer   Game17:30  AIsland finals @ Foyer       Tickets 2017     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venue</title>
      <link>http://joyofcoding.org/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 12:38:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://joyofcoding.org/venue/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating the art, craft, science and joy of software development ―&amp;nbsp; Our 2017 venue: De Rotterdamse Schouwburg
   Joy of Coding 2017 will take place at the Rotterdamse Schouwburg, a theatre in the centre of Rotterdam. While this venue usually hosts dance, theatre and music theatre productions, it offers ideal conference facilities. The location is on the central Rotterdam square of the same name, Schouwbergplein.
 Getting there Address: Rotterdamse Schouwburg, Schouwburgplein 25, 3012 CL Rotterdam</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>